[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Valentine's Day is
about spreading love,
not just to couples,
to everyone.
It's like a virus, but
with glitter and consent.
[DOCTOR] Help!
[NED] I'm going
to get you, witch!
I really hate working
on this floor!
Spread love, Mr. Ned!
Oh, calm down, Ned!
The only thing you
ever caught is syphilis!
Yes, babe, I promise I got you
something really nice
for Valentine's Day.
[COURIER] Oh, delivery.
Thank you.
Let me guess.
Boyfriend's pearls?
They're for my girlfriend.
I'm working a double shift,
so I had them sent here.
Is that Mr. Ned?
He's always saying he likes
my gorgeous blonde locks.
Meth makes everything
seem natural!
[DONDON SIGHS] It's packed.
Overflow?
Again?
Hi, Mr. Ned!
[MOUTHING] Sorry.
Gorgeous.
Yeah.
I don't want those
flowers shedding
on the nurses' station, George.
[NOA] Hey, guys!
A little help, please?
- [NED SNARLING]
- [DONDON] No, Mr. Walker! Bad!
[DONDON] Get down! No!
[FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TESS YAWNING]
Are you dating that guy
with the lazy eye again?
I wasn't sure if he was looking
at my face or my chest.
Ew, Mom! No!
That was in nursing school.
He was the only one who
gave you flowers before.
So I thought...
Wait, who gave that?
Nobody.
You better tell me.
[NOA] No one!
Then why didn't you
put it in your office?
Why are you hiding it here?
Here, put this somewhere
before it ends in the dumpster.
Hm!
- Where?
- In your butthole!
Figure it out!
- [NOA GROANING]
- No, no, no!
Ros, can you call security?
Bigfoot has a higher chance
of showing up.
You want me to page him too?
Oh, cute flowers.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TESS SCOFFS]
I'm gonna kill him.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRIM CHUCKLING]
- [TRICKLING]
Why did you give my daughter
flowers and cake?
[GRIM SCOFFS]
I can stand being in this body.
But I cannot conduct such a
vulgar function while you stare.
Oh, are you insecure?
Go away!
And stop messing
with my daughter!
[WATER RUNNING]
[GRIM] I guess I can do that.
Will you come with me then?
Don't you have any
other spirit you can annoy?
Death is a department, Tess,
not a one-man show.
[TESS] Fine.
Then I open my mouth and
I tell Noa and you're done.
Oh, you will do no such thing.
Watch me.
- [SNAPS]
- [ENERGY BURSTING]
[TESS EXHALES SHARPLY]
What did you just do?
[SIGHS] Look, I may not be able
to control free will...
But I can make things
even harder for the dead.
What were you going
to say again?
I'm gonna tell Noa
that you're a...
You're nothing but a...
Yeah.
I thought so.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[ATZIN] (In Spanish)
I’m here as your translator,
so patients like you can receive
proper information.
The doctor diagnosed you with
Takotsubo Cardiomyopathy.
(In Spanish) What’s that?
It’s a heart condition
called Takotsubo.
Otherwise known as
Heartbreak Syndrome.
That's a thing?
(In Spanish) Give me a second,
I'll Google it first.
Listen.
This reminds me of the time
when I had a heartbreak.
I missed an audition
for Brillante Mendoza.
It's not even my fault
that I was late.
My assistant got me
the wrong shade of foundation.
I couldn't make myself appear
looking like that!
I fired her.
My heart healed,
and my pores tightened.
- Instantly.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Go on.
I thought
I could understand English,
but I have no clue
what she’s saying.
Uh, she escaped from somewhere.
Let me get you a real nurse.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Where--
Hey, has anybody seen
my Valentine's Day gifts?
Check lost and found.
Or the trash.
But it's V-Day, who would just
throw away presents like that?
Ros.
[PHONE BUZZING]
[GEORGE] Oh, I'm dead.
Like, I'm actually dead.
[PHONE BUZZING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[COVER THUDS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOA SNIFFS DEEPLY]
[COVER THUDS]
[FLOWERS RUSTLING]
[VASE RATTLING]
Just flowers and cake, and
you're already head over heels?
How pitiful.
What? It's Mango Supreme,
your favorite.
It's a gift.
- Normal people do that.
- Normal?
I mean, he is a bit younger
than me.
Younger? Ha!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR KNOB CLICKS OPEN]
You wanted to see me?
Yeah! I wanted to thank you
for those.
- My God, Noa, he's--
- Oh, so you think--
- Get away from there!
- I did! I did give them to you!
I'm heading to the cafeteria
for lunch,
- if you'd like to join me.
- Don't!
My treat as a thank you.
Yeah, sure!
Okay.
[TESS SCOFFS]
- Let's go.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
Lol-lol-lol-lol.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHEELS RATTLING]
Ros?
Uh, where are my flowers?
- How should I know?
- They said you threw them out.
[WHEELS SCREECH]
Who said that?
Tell me.
Or I'm going to stuff you
in that plastic bag,
like all the valentine trash
I'm cleaning up.
Hey!
You two!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
What nonsense
are you two spreading?
Ros?
- What's going on?
- Nothing, Doc.
Only one thing I really hate
more than this dumb holiday...
...is liars and cheaters.
Dang, lady,
who broke your heart?
She's serious, guys.
You better speak up.
N-No, I swear, Ros.
Nothing about you.
[ROS GROWLING]
Say it!
Flowers, Noa, lunch. Together.
[ROSS GROWLING]
We swear!
We only heard it
in the break room.
- From someone else.
- Who?!
[GRIM EXHALES]
I'm so glad we went back
for the cake.
[GRIM GROANING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
This is delicious.
[GRIM CHUCKLING]
[NOA CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Um...
I know I said it was my treat,
but 50 dollars?
That's a lot for lunch.
[NOA CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Is it?
[GRIM GROANING]
You look like you haven't eaten
in days!
Millenia, actually.
[NOA CHUCKLES]
That's so funny.
[GRIM GROANING]
So, I hate secrets,
and not knowing stuff.
- So...
- Yeah?
Tell me about yourself, Grim.
Like, why did your parents
name you that?
Sounds kind of deathly.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yeah.
I have many names.
[GRIM CHUCKLING]
[DONDON] So, basically,
the heart gets like
super sad or whatever,
and the left ventricle weakens.
See? I'm smart.
- What broke your heart?
- Oh, no, I'm not--
I dated a guy
without a profile pic.
Not you.
I regret involving
her too, sorry.
[CAMILLE] So, you can
tell us anything.
It's not like you're in a gossip
show or anything like that.
You know, I stopped doing that
years ago--
Mostly.
- You can tell us.
- Uh...
My boyfriend...
of 15 years...
Um...
I met him yesterday.
- She says that--
- No, no, I know that word.
"Novio" means party.
Or is that the conjugation?
It actually means boyfriend,
but yeah, close, whatever.
[CAMILLE] You know,
when I headlined
that Saturday teen sketch
show, Bulilit...
I had no heartbreak.
I didn't experience that
because boyfriends are for those
who don't have fan clubs.
My chest...
Guys, guys, guys.
Are those numbers
supposed to spike like that?
[EKG BEEPING RAPIDLY]
Ah, so we're all pretending
- I'm invisible now?
- Did you enjoy lunch?
Don't blame me if you're lonely.
You work too much!
- Yeah, when's the next one?
- Don't act nice, Grim!
Grim. Your parents
really committed to that.
Yeah, but let's not talk
about me.
Are you dating anyone?
Are you curious?
How would you like it
if I never move on, huh?!
There was one guy.
But Ros says that he shops
in the same aisle.
Hm.
[ROS GASPS]
They're right!
Grim gave your flowers
and cake to Noa.
[COVER THUDS]
And now I'm hungry.
[PHONE BUZZING]
- [PHONE BUZZING]
- [GEORGE SIGHS]
Dude, I'm going to punch
someone, I swear to God!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you picking on me because
you grew up without a father,
or because I didn't allow you
to date until you're 21?
- I'm not!
- Stranger danger!
Don't punch him yet.
I need my camera.
[PHONE BUZZING]
[GRIM] So, did you enjoy
our time together?
No, the guy should pay
for lunch!
[PHONE BUZZES]
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
Grim!
I taught him that.
Who told you
that you could give
my Red Ribbon cake
and flowers to Noa?
Huh? What-- What flowers?
I told you, it's not from him!
He's a--
- [ROS] Punch him already!
- Yeah, do it.
Wait, you bought those flowers
for me?
[ROS] No,
it's for his boyfriend!
George!
Babe!
He's... a she?
(In Tagalog)
Didn't see that coming either.
[INTERCOM CHIMING]
[DONDON ON SPEAKER] Um...
Is this on?
Camille,
is this the right button?
Paging Nurse Noa!
Code, um...
Yeah, I'm not totally
sure what to say, but like...
Come to Room 5-0...
Wait, Camille,
is it 5-0...
Yeah, it's 5-0-0.
Okay, thanks, bye!
[RECEIVER CLICKS]
That's it.
I'm really starting
to hate Valentine's Day.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- [NOA SIGHS SHARPLY]
- What is it?
- Is that normal?
Of course it's not.
Why hasn't anyone
paged the attending?
She has a heartbreak.
[SIGHS] Heartbreak?
You want to hear
about heartbreak, Camille?
I just spent the entire day
thinking someone
actually sent me flowers.
I mean, who does that?
Me!
I live here.
I chart here.
I nap by the vending machine.
My crush, who I thought was gay,
actually has a girlfriend.
And the guy who
supposedly sent me flowers?
Total fraud! Of course.
(In Tagalog) See? I told you so!
(In English) That's it!
I hate Valentine's Day.
Cupid can choke.
Well, if he's a real angel,
I'm sorry.
[SNICKERS, LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
Oh my god!
I am so sorry.
I thought you were unconscious.
You're right.
(In Spanish) It sucks.
[LAUGHING]
(In English) Hi, I'm Noa.
(In Spanish) Hello, I'm Amore.
(In English) Nice to meet you.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Hey, look!
Her levels are improving.
[MACHINE BEEPING STEADILY]
- [CHUCKLES]
- Wonderful!
[CAMILLE SCOFFS]
Imagine how many
lives would be saved
if HIPAA allows me
to post about this.
[CHUCKLES]
Look, we're not
out of the woods yet,
but that laugh
bought us some time.
(In Spanish)
You're very funny.
[CHUCKLES, SNORTS]
(In English) It's okay.
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
[INHALES, EXHALES HEAVILY]
- Hey.
- What happened? I kept calling.
I know, sorry.
Work just got really crazy.
I-I got you some stuff.
Thank you.
[GEORGE SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Psst!
Um...
Give me just one minute.
I'll meet you at the benches.
Okay.
[COMICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- What?
- Here.
Is this an apology?
My Valentine's gift.
And I realized...
I was the gossip and the liar.
That wasn't just a running gag?
Um, yeah, sure.
Let's go with that.
It's okay.
I know you'd love me
no matter what.
[ROS CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Happy Valentine's, dude.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISTLES]
[GEORGE CHUCKLES]
[GRIM]
You wanted to see me?
- Please, have a seat.
- [TESS SCOFFS]
(In Tagalog)
You're in trouble.
(In English)
You can stop pretending
you don't see her now.
[GRIM CHUCKLES]
[EXHALES]
I think I'll sit over here.
[GRUNTS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What gave it away?
How much time do we have?
I don't know.
Not long.
Right, Tess?
(In Tagalog) I will be here
as long my daughter needs me.
(In English) Yeah,
but you feel it, don't you?
Your tether to this world
is loosening.
You think ghosts can just
wander around in purgatory
for the rest of time?
Hmm?
- He's lying.
- No, I'm not.
[HUFFS]
You have your chain of command.
I have mine.
Bureaucracy exists everywhere,
living or dead.
Someone's always going to
get chewed up, right?
The mystery is...
who gets bit first.
(In Tagalog)
Wow, you're good.
You're like The Riddler.
So mysterious.
Where's Batman?
(In English)
So, am I being fired?
I was really starting
to enjoy the food here.
No.
Look, I've seen you help people.
You don't have to take them,
you can save them.
Well, since I'm not being fired,
I have to get back to work.
I didn't say you can go.
Well, I'm on the clock, so...
We both know how this works.
Every rule shattered
demands its due.
That's how it works.
That's the truth.
Then I'll pay it.
Now you can go.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
I have the sudden urge to do
a 30 French Foley,
front full insertion.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
What was that about?
Nothing.
Happy Valentine's Day, babe.
Happy Valentine's, babe.
George!
Yes, babe?
Who's Noa?
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]